well
hello my name is big buck bunny
you might know me from such films as big
back bunny
for today i've been asked to tell you
about 3d
mice and how they can make your life
easier
as a digital artist traditionally the
creation of
digital three-dimensional content has
relied on two-dimensional input devices
over time this can result in a sore arm
as well as some less than appetizing
visuals
well fortunately there are better ways
of
doing this in the real
world objects have many dimensions
and we interact with our surroundings
with two hands
you wouldn't build an apple with just
one hand would you
once upon a time we only had access to
simple
two-dimensional input devices this meant
that replicating natural interactions
with computers was
difficult a 3d mouse really makes a
difference working with a 3d mouse in
one hand
and the standard mouse in the other you
can access
and interact with all three dimensions
at the same time and it's more
air-cooked air well
let's just say it feels good
with 3d mouse actions like panning
zooming and rotating
certainly just make a whole lot of sense
indeed interaction between you and your
computer
has never been so real with more than a
million
treaty my sold there are a whole lot of
people using them
from engineers to artists from
architects to geographers
even gamers
ah i feel like a young bunny again so
you see people from all kinds of
backgrounds and industries
are using 3d mice to make their lives
easier and more fun
i already have mine shouldn't you also
get one
soon
you